A Guide to the Keswick Hunt Club Ephemera 1949-1986, 1998
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Keswick Hunt Club Epehemera 1949-1986, 1998
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
11383
ca. 485 items (2 Hollinger boxes, ca. .5 linear foot)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
The collection is without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection, originally a gift from Mr. & Mrs. Linton Massey, was transferred from the Rare Books Division Ephemera File to the Manuscripts Division, Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library, Charlottesville, Virginia, on February 19, 1998.
Scope and Content Information
This collection consists of the papers of the Keswick Hunt Club, Albemarle County, Virginia, ca. 1949-1986, 1998, ca. 485 items (2 Hollinger boxes, ca. .5 linear foot), and contains form letters; invitations to dinners, dances, horse shows, Keswick Hunt Club Balls, and other social events; schedules; treasurer's reports; short articles on "Champion Hunter of Virginia" and "Field Rules of Foxhunting"; notices of events and meetings; fixture cards; membership lists; newsletters; and other ephemera mailed to members of the club.
Contents List
- Annual Meetings 1955-1986 (Box 1)
- "Champion Hunter of Virginia" and "Field Rules of Foxhunting" n.d. (Box 1)
- Fixture Cards 1952-1986, n.d., 2 folders (Box 1)
- Form Letters to Membership 1955-1986, n.d. (Box 1)
- Hunter Trials 1969-1985 (Box 1)
- Invitations to Dances, Dinners & Other Social Events 1949-1986, n.d., 2 folders (Box 1)
- Invitations--Keswick Horse Show Dinners 1953-1985 (Box 1)
- Keswick Hunt Club Balls 1962-1986 (Box 2)
- Membership Lists 1967-1982 (Box 2)
- Neighborhood Horse Show 1953-1986 (Box 2)
- Newsletters 1961-1975 (Box 2)
- Response Postal Cards 1954-1983, n.d. (Box 2)
- Treasurer's Reports 1957-1985 (Box 2)
- Working Terrier Trials 1978-1981 (Box 2)